Welcome to exercise number 54.
We are asked to write a function to reverse the link, at least recursively.
We have seen this method and we have read it written in the previous video, and we need to transform
this into the recursive way.
So I will create a method called public returns not.
And it is called the reverse list recursively.
It took into the party meeting on in the same way that we have done before, and we start if had equal
equal to none or that had the next equal equal to null if it does not contain any elements.
Or if it contains only one nod, then return and hand.
OK, so if you have a one piece, how to reverse one note.
If you read it from the left or the right, it would be the same result, it would be one.
No.
OK.
This is the case of one, one or no nonsense.
The second step is covering that and reversing the restless book, reversing the rest of the list.
We start not for arrests equal to reverse.
We are calling a function recursively.
Had the next OK, then had the next dot next equal to hand.
We are making it more and more recursively.
And here it will stop, so it will call this method again.
Go and one many times.
Please go back to the recursion section to learn more about this type and this pattern of recursion.
OK.
This is the recursion symbol, and it will be called until there is a returning of the one function,
one function return that its components and it will be stored at rest.
It will continue executing that program and go back to that to execute the rest of that block.
OK.
Three.
We need to make had that next equal to now.
So the head head now becomes null.
So had the head reference.
For next week, now becomes now had the next equal to No.
And four fix the head pointer.
OK, so it will return.
All right.
OK, we have created a reverse list recursively.
This is the method we will check if one or more or no notes, if there is no notes.
Our one, it will be recursively or it will be reversed.
The same if.
If there is more than one node inside the link, at least, then we are going to reverse it using the
reverse list recursively method and we pass had the next, had the next and so on until reaching the
end.
After reaching the end, it will reverse this and will be executed and a returning type of no node and
node.
This returning type of node will be stored inside Greece and the rest of the program will be executed
completely and so on until reaching the had had the next equal to none and then returning to rest.
OK, let's test this in the main link at least not pretend last link at least time the reverse list
recursively name could list of.
OK, let's run and see.
This is here.
I.
System of brain to reverse this.
Three, five, one four four.
Maybe this would not be executed.
Reverses the recursively.
Irish puppeteer and bass.
Simply link unless the reverse thing could list, and I think it hit list.
Ted?
And that is not the.
Because it is reversed.
OK.
So we are not going to call this method before I will run it.
And maybe there is a problem here.
Had Dot next to link at last Dot had.
Oh, OK.
I think here is the problem.
I pass.
It has had.
Let's run and see again.
And here we go, guys.
This is the list before reversing.
And this is their reversed list recursively three, five, one and four.
OK, so this is very good to understand the errors and understand how to solve them.
And we have done a very big part of Link.
At least we still have one or two more exercises about Link, at least like rotation.
And by that, we can say that we have finished that single.